Lilia Ito's Aim: Become a Pokémon Master
Yes, sir.
More than that...
Oh!
Good morning.
What?
What a surprise.
I'm opening all of these right now.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I know, but...
It's been a long time. It's been a long time.
I can't get the card.
I get a diagnosis about once a month.
I couldn't get it at all, and even if I could get it, I had to re-sell it.
I've been having a hard time getting them, because there's been a little time lag.
But this time, I'm free on the same day.
This is the newest one that's out right now.
We have three boxes of it. And listen...
I really did stop by the convenience store on the way here today, and I found this...
I've never seen Pokemon cards in a convenience store before.
I was wondering if they even had them at convenience stores.
But it just so happened that they had them, and they told us that we could only buy one pack per person.
I bought a pack, so I'd like to open it up now.
It's been too long since I've seen them, so I'm feeling a little distant or strange.
He's so cute!
I saw it on the radio.
Minor child
I love it!
Yes, after all, Gaburius is the star this time.Yes, after all, the star of the show this time is Gabrius.
You see, he's right here in the middle.
You see?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
This time...
This time, it was taken before the recording.
So it's different from usual.
It's different from usual.
Gabriel is... the main character this time.
Gaburius is the main character this time.
Gaburius EX.
I want to get it.
What do you think?
Great...
I want Gaburius, too... but...
What I'm after is...
Chiri.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I really want Chiri-chan.
I want Chiri for sure!
I'm a Scubai player.
Grusha is one of the Scubai...
Oh!
Here it is!
Yay!
Can you see it?
I hope you can see me.Can you see it?
It seems so rare when it sparkles like this.
Let's go back to what I said before.
I want Grusha.
But I'm...
But next to that...
I really like Chiri-chan.
So I really want to win Chiri-chan.
So I dressed up like Chiri-chan.
I've dressed like Chiri-chan.
I'm going to win for sure!
That's what I'm determined to do!
But I really don't care if it's SR or SR.
I really don't care if it's SR or SR.
Yes... the parasol lady...
She's here...
Not too good!
Too good.
Yeah, I know.
She's so cool.
I love it.
Oh, plus, there's a minus in this one.
It's in the box.
I have this art rare.
It's so cute.
I've been thinking about it ever since it was announced.
Oh! It's Mr. Yukihara!
It's Mr. Yukihara!
We were talking about art rarities and Mr. Yukihara came in!
He's so cute! Cute.
I recently put together a Myraidon deck.
Last time I was at Okeydoko.
I performed at Okeydoko.
I played against Hikaru Takahashi.
At that time
Hikaru was using Myraidon.
And I lost.
I was...
My opponent's deck.
I thought Myrideon was really good.
And...
Recently, that CL deck...
I wonder if it's called CL.
Wasn't there a CL?
I don't know if it's called a tournament.
It was a Pokemon card tournament.
I was watching it.
And there were a lot of people who were using Myrideon.
And there were a lot of people using Mylidon.
I thought it was really cool.
I thought it was great.
And the winner had a Myraidon deck.
The winner had a Myrideon deck.
I thought it was really cool!
I thought it was really cool.
The next day or so after I saw that
I built it the next day or so.
That's right. Yes, and I've always
I like deck types and stuff.
I used to hold something like Arces Laicheu.
Oh!
Wow!
Isn't he so cool?
This is the next best thing to the Klaus Luhr miner.
I've been after that one.
Oh, my God!
That's so cool!
I think I'm going to put this on the back of my cell phone.
If I put two of them in there...
I'll put it on the back of my cell phone.
I'll put this one on the back of my cell phone.
I have an old card called "Bad White Dragon".
He gave it to me.
That's what I'm putting in there.
Don't you just want to put this Cloud in there?
I love you guys!
So I'll be happy with whatever I get.
But when you come to Klaus Luhrmeiner...
Oh! Older EX!
I love it!
I knew it would sparkle like crazy on terrastal.
Look, it's a little...
It's different.
Well, it's still standing.
Yes! Gilgard is here. Yes! Gilgard is here!
This art rare is so beautiful!
What can I say?
Isn't it too cool?
Isn't the lineup awesome?
It's so good!
I knew it!
I really like cards with special illustrations like this.
I really like them.
It's always the first one.
I don't know, in the beginning.
The good ones.
Sometimes I pull it out.
Oh! That's good.
Yay!
I knew taking a video of the opening would be awesome.
Here comes the paraplegic sister!
Oh! Oh my gosh!
I'm shaking when I see a girl's SR up close like this!
She's too cute!
What! So cute! Oh my God!
Oh, my God, where do I put it?
Where do I put it?
One-box finished.
Wow.
Seriously, when you pull in the opening video...
I don't often pull out SR Pokemon, do I? Me...
feel like I pull a lot of support SRs.
Whenever I make a video I don't know, it's always when I'm doing a video.
When I pull it at home at all.
I'm pretty sure it's a Pokémon SR when I'm at home.
when the camera is rolling.
Aww...
Oh no!
Now, I'd like to open the second box.
Well, I've opened so many boxes.
I have a lot of Pokemon cards at home
but I haven't been able to organize them
I haven't been able to organize them.
Even if I want to make a deck
Pokémon are Pokémon, and tools are tools.
Tools are tools, supports are supports, and so on.
Energy is energy, and so on.
But I don't separate them by type, or by order of 50 on the card.
I really don't know what's where.
So you have to look at them one by one.
So, in fact, they're all sorted by 50-on.
I'd like to put Pokémon by type and so on.
Oh, wow!
Ugh, here comes Pai-X.
Wow, it's a Terrastre too!
This is really cool!
I like it.
I wonder what kind of decks people are building right now.
I heard the other day...
I heard some people talking about putting together an Oziran deck.
That's cool.
Whoa, naughty, naughty.Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You scared the shit out of me.
It's an ex-lizard.
Wow.
It's cute.
It's like a bicycle parking lot or something.
They're all lined up in a row.
Ex-lizards are nice, aren't they?
He asked me to show him all the decks.
You've been saying that a lot in the videos.
In the comments.
I read them.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know if that's a good idea.
There are a lot of people with unexpected decks.
Like decks that are used a lot.
There's a high tier.
Strong decks that are often used in tournaments.
Oh, wow.
Second Ganburi Asli X!
I'm so happy.
Seriously, you can never have too many.
Thank you so much.
I thought I wasn't enough.
Oh, wow!
Here it is!
I got the SR for Hooper EX.
What?
Wow! Wow!
Let's take a look and compare.
Wow!
I got a SR, but...
No, Artrea, really, please!
Please come!
Oh, here it comes!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
That's great!
I was just saying that.
It's the one I've been waiting for.
It's the Prasl art rarity.
Isn't it cute?
And now there's a minor version, too.
I want to have both of them in my collection, you know?
I'm so happy for you!
I recently bought a pair of those socks from Louise.
Louise's!
Oh!
Nutley.
Oh, my God.
That's beautiful.
Nutley, he's smiling so much. Look.
He's smiling.
Ha-ha-ha.
He's so cute.
It's just that Minor didn't show up.
But Nutley's not here yet.But, Nutley, we haven't left yet.
It's okay.
Okay, so...
EVOX... it's done.
That's how it went down.
SR is this EX.
It's amazing!
It's really sparkling.
It's nice.
And...
I've been waiting for it.
Prasul is here.
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy.
I think I found it here, too, because it's the same one I was looking for.
That's good.
No more Art Rares, please.
Ha-ha-ha.
Now the third box...
I'd like to open the third box.
Next.
Um...
Diagnostics.
And information.
Oh, here it is.
Oh!
I got it.
Ha-ha-ha.
Kabuko-keko-ex.
It hadn't come out yet.They weren't out yet.
I knew you liked electric types.
I'd like to release as many as possible
I'd like to bring out as many as I can.
You're the third one.
Ha-ha-ha.
You just said you wanted to make sure there's no overlap.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
You've got a lot of visitors.
Just looking at you.
Oh, wow.
So cute!
You're on top of Wampachi.
It's so cute!
Here comes Batur's art rarity.
I've never seen you before.
Ha-ha-ha.
Wow, it's so cute!
I love it!
So many different Pokémon on one card.
on one card.
I love the fact that there are other Pokémon
I love the fact that there are other Pokémon on the card.
Oh!
Goblios...
Goblios.
Three in a row?
Ha-ha-ha.Ha-ha-ha.
Wow, wait a minute, I'm scared.
I'm already getting a little scared.
Three, three.
Oh, my God, there's a lot in here?
Oh, my God!
I got a pair. I got a pair.
What? Mamin?
Oh, my God, you're right.
I see.
Yes! Oh!
That's right!
Yes, so I finished opening the package.
It's kind of a mess, opening
I've been in the mood to open the box
I was opening it like I was opening a pack of boxes
I was opening it like I was opening a pack of boxes.
But it wasn't a box at all.
but 30 packs of pieces.
So this is the result.
This is how it turned out.
I mean, it's not like it's no good.
My grandpa.
I came in here looking like a grandpa.
I didn't see him at all.
I'm sad.
Ha-ha-ha.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Good morning. What?
You scared me. You scared me.
Why?
Please, excuse me.
You scared the shit out of me. Good morning.
Good morning. Good morning.
Is this a Pokemon? Yes! Yes, it is.
I don't know anything about Pokemon, but I came here.
Oh, I see.
I'm so surprised.
Excuse me.
Nagi-chan came to see me.
I just opened it.
Oh, is this all of them?
After they were opened? Yes, there's only one left.
There's only one more card.
There are so many cards.
Did you just open all of these?
Yes.
What's this one?
This one.
That's the one you just opened.
And this one you just opened.
The one you just opened and the one you just opened?
Yes.
What do you want me to say?
What should I say?
Well, one box.
There's, like, 30 packs in each of these boxes.
That's roughly what's in this box.
That's a lot of food.An amazing amount of
Oh, my God.
Look at the trash cans.
Amazing amount of trash.
Ha-ha-ha
That's amazing!
That's really great.
I don't recognize the card.
I know, right?
Not really.
But I'm kind of interested.
But it's a little late to start.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What about video games?
You've never played games?
Pokemon?
DS games.
The first one.
Not 3DS, but DS.
It came in different colors.
It's really choppy.
But I can see it.
What? But it's a generation.
I mean, it's not like it's tiny.
Oh, yeah.
Then it was a long time ago.
That's mine.
Wow!
I couldn't get any further.
Oh, I see.Ah, yes.
Pokemon on DS and
Dracula
Dracula doesn't even have a slime.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're not that good at video games?
No, I'm not that good.
But I know that one.
At least Pikachu.
If I didn't know better...
I'd be pretty surprised.
Pikachu, Pichu, Pichu...
Like Pipichu.
Ping pichu
I don't know.
Pipichu is different.
Why don't we do at least three?
Pichu.
Pikachu.
There's another one...
Pikachu
Pikadragon
Not quite a dragon.
No, it won't.
Pikadragon is bad.
Pikachu is
Pikachu is on top of
Pikachu is called "Lightning Choo".It's called thunder chu.
I wonder if it's gone.
No pica.
What?
What's that sound?
But, um...
What? What?
Um...
I think it's a Pokemon card.
I like to illustrate something.
An artist...
He did it.
Just one card. It's a camogie course.
Camoroni?
I don't know. This duck.
I said duck!
Duckweed is done.
It's really done.
At least.
This just, oh, that's right.
It says "Tamagiko 23.
I wonder what it is.
I was surprised. I was surprised because it's here right now.
Oh, wow.
Are you playing a game right now?
No, not at all. I'm just opening it.
You see, the picture has a totally different touch.
It's cute.
It's amazing. It's an unknown world.
It's an unknown world. There are so many colors. It is an unknown world. There are many colors.
There are all kinds of attributional things.
Yes, yes, attribute-attribute-attribute.
Then take a look at this.
By all means.
If you like.
Lastly, I bought this at the convenience store right here.
It just happened to be on sale.
Really?
That's great, that's great, that's great.
Isn't it great?
I went to buy some cafe au lait.
And I found a pack of it, and I gave it to Nagi-chan.
Can I put one of these inside?
No, there are five in the pack.
Can I have one of those?
Which one is more interesting?
That one's the back, so that one's fine.
Around here.
Around here, okay?
Wow, that's fresh.
Here we go! Here!
Meteno.
This is a rare card.
Looks like a serve.
Maybe not.
Measure the chairs, okay? It's Nintendo.
Here comes the second one.
It's fresh, but it's amazing. It's fresh, but it's amazing.
These are tools.
Oh, so you have tools?
Yes, there's a card.
Here comes the third card.
What card?
This one.
Sleeping Bugs.
It's a water type.
Is it here?
Right here.
Interesting.
I don't understand.
Here we go.
This one.
Hippovid.
Gabyte.
And when it evolves...
When it evolves, it becomes... this.
It's the prototype.
Yes, it does.
Gabrious.
Last one.
This one.
Nice.
Jirachi.
He's so cute.
The girls love him.You're popular with the girls.
It's all right.
It's fun.
It's like a photo shoot.
It's true.
I'd like to collect them and guess my favorite.
Who's your guess?
My guess is...
A girl named Chiri.
Isn't she cool?
Beautiful girls are so good.
She's very nice.
You seem to like her.
Here.
I'm a girl.
Kansai civilization.
I can't imagine.
That's why you're so strong.
Do people have strength?
No, no, no.
It's a Pokémon battle.
As a game.
As opponents.
Humans.
We don't battle.
I thought I was out of the world
I thought I was out of the world.
It's not a fighting game.
I just started playing a game a few minutes ago.
Oh, yeah.Right.
Pokemon games...
You always get two together, don't you?
That's a little complicated.
I don't know which one to get.
I don't know.
I don't care which one you get.
You know, your favorite color.
It doesn't matter.
It's just that this one looks better.
I've heard a lot of people say they bought this one because it's cooler.
If you're interested...
I'd love to hear from you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so happy.
It's really funny.
Really?
I'm just ignorant?
When I talk to you, Lanie.
I think you're kind of funny.
It's fun.
Really?
You're Lilia, so you're easy to talk to.
What? No way.
Yeah.
Of all the first-term students...
She's the one who talks.
Lani...
You have great hobbies.
I'm glad.Glad to hear it.
Yes, so
Raging Surf distribution is over.
Lani came to see me, too
Yes
What a surprise!
I don't know what to do
face.
What am I supposed to do?
It's okay.
Just be here.
I'm glad you're here.
That was fun.
I'm glad
With someone who knows and likes Pokemon
It's fun to talk about it, but
but teaching it to people who don't know it
I'm so happy to know that it's so much fun
I'm glad
I hope you'll take this opportunity
I'd be happy if you could do it too, Lilia.
Of course.
Yes, I'll see you later.
Next time.
I hope we can open the next one.
I'll do my best.
Okay, by the way
Please give me a like and a high rating!
I'll be waiting for your comments!I'll be waiting for your comments by all means!
Bye-bye!